这里很明显就是客厅啦
Obviously, this is the living room.
活动室里的酒柜有很多酒
There's a fully stocked bar in the den,
家庭影院在楼下
and the home theater is downstairs.
厉害了 你老板创建一个时尚网站
Wow. So, your boss launches one style website
就能过上这么豪华的生活啊
and she can afford all of this?
真希望"五零年代深柜爸爸"风格
I wish "1950s closeted father"
也是观众争相追捧
was a look people were clamoring for.
才没那么简单
Oh, it is not that simple.
我们公司的胜利方程式非常具体
The formula for NERP is very specific --
过气女明星加迷之自信
former actress plus confidence based on nothing
等于售出数百万的可疑健康产品
equals millions in sales of iffy wellness products.
我们应该送她一份礼物 感谢她让我们借住
We should get her a gift for letting us stay here,
但该送什么给一个正在斯里兰卡
but what do you give someone who's researching
研究木炭牙刷的人呢
charcoal toothbrushes in Sri Lanka?
事实上 她正在明斯克
Oh, actually, she's judging
给胎盘烹饪大赛当评审呢
a placenta-cooking contest in Minsk.
那我们还是别碰冰箱里的东西了
Maybe we should stay away from the fridge.
我们已经到酒庄了
So, we're in wine country.
品酒活动何时开始
When does the wine tasting start,
因为被公众狠狠抨击后
because I can use it after
我真心需要喝一杯
the public bashing I've had to endure.
又来了 别一哭二闹了 曼尼
Here we go. No more boo-hooing, Manny.
评论没那么糟
The review wasn't that bad.
他说我扮演的大侦探波罗
He called my portrayal of Inspector Poirot
"不真实" "不可信"
"Unconvincing," "Not believable,"
"难以信服" 还有"讽刺地多余"
"Hard to buy," and "Ironically redundant".
米奇 小卡
Hey, Mitch, Cam,
你们已经有一晚时间好好思考我的表演了
now that you guys have had a chance to sleep on my performance,
你们有什么看法
what did you think?
-那角色不好演 -没错 不怪你
- It was a tricky part. - Yeah, and I don't blame you.
只能怪选你去演的人
I blame whoever cast you.
还有几件事
Okay, a couple more things.
终于轮到介绍衣橱了
Finally, the closet part of the tour.
我老板给你们每人都留了一件特别的浴袍
My boss left each of you a very special robe.
穿上后 浴袍能抑制炎症
They minimize inflammation
同时为你的肌肤轻柔去角质
and gently exfoliate your skin whilst you wear them.
真古怪 我只看到六件浴袍
That's weird. I only see six robes.
它们是这点让你觉得古怪吗
That's what's weird about them?
还有一件事
Oh, one last thing --
千万别碰厅里展出的小皇冠
Do not touch the tiara on display in the drawing room.
那非常容易打烂
It is very delicate.
明白了吗
Got it?
抱歉女儿 你又露出那个样子了
Sorry, honey. You're just -- You're doing that thing
看起来就像只很紧绷的小鹿
where you look like a really intense baby deer.
你越想做出凶狠的表情
Oh, the scarier you try to be,
-反而越可爱 -就是啊
- the more adorable you are. ?- I know!
随便了
Whatever. I have, like,
我还要帮我老板干无数的活儿
a million errands to run for my boss.
等一下 既然没人预先说要睡主卧室
Hang on. Since, uh, no one's called dibs on the master bedroom,
我想应该是先到先得了吧
I assume it's up for grabs.
事实上 楼上只有三间客房
Oh, actually, there are only three guest bedrooms upstairs,
所以你得睡在那里了
so you'll have to sleep in there, okay?
佣人房吗
The maid's quarters?
但那样我就睡在嘎吱作响的门旁边...
But I'll be right next to the creaky do--
你想的话 我可以给门上点润滑油
You know, if you want, I can put some oil on that.
千万不可
Oh, no, no, no. Don't.
这是西藏传统的吱吱响铰链
These are traditional Tibetan creaking hinges.
咱也得买一个
We need those.
-悠着点喝 -相信我 爸爸
- Whoa. Go easy. - ?Trust me, Dad.
此刻我真的很需要酒精
Right now, I could really use this.
先把这话说明白 我爱菲尔
I love Phil. Let's just get that out of the way first,
但他有一双熊熊拖鞋
but he has these bear slippers.
我不知道从哪儿来的
I don't know where they came from,
大概是从也卖尾戒
probably the same place that sells
和其他鬼东西 让你对你老公
pinky rings and other things that make it difficult
难以产生性欲的地方买的
to see your husband as a sexual being.
哎呀 我打赤脚[熊爪]应该不能进来
Oh, my gosh. I don't think I'm allowed here in my bare feet.
幸好 我有个妙招
Fortunately, I have a tactic
可以甩掉我不喜欢的东西
for getting rid of things that I hate.
我建议菲尔带拖鞋来度假
I suggest that Phil brings them on vacation,
然后我"忘记"打包带回去
and then I forget to repack them.
谢谢
Thanks.
印着美元符号的领带
Dollar-sign necktie --
我一手甩进尼亚加拉大瀑布
I flung it over Niagara Falls.
用水钻拼出"皮条客"的皮带扣
The belt buckle with "Pimp" in crystals?
狠狠投入大峡谷
Chucked it in the Grand Canyon.
我想知道歌洛莉亚在加拉帕戈斯岛
Huh. I wonder if that's what Gloria did
是不是也用这招让我的牛仔背心消失
to my denim vest in the Galapagos.
我只需今晚偷溜出来
I just gotta sneak out tonight
把熊拖鞋扔进树林深处就行了
and disappear those bear slippers in the woods.
我是个坏人吗
Am I a terrible person?
不是 但你可能有污染国家公园的
No, but there might be a pattern of desecrating national parks
作案模式 最好注意一下
you might want to look at.
别吃了 小胖
That's enough, Chubs.
你在干吗
What are you doing?
斯黛拉最近非常消沉
Stella's been severely depressed
因为她最好的朋友诺曼
because her best friend, Norman,
也就是邻居的狗 刚刚死了
the next-door neighbor's dog, just died.
她连最喜欢的绝招都不做了
She won't even do her favorite trick anymore.
斯黛拉
Stella.
斯黛拉 说话
Stella, speak.
说话啊 就像你在说"哈啰"
Speak. Like you're saying "Hello".
啊呜 汪汪哈啰
Hellooo! Hel-Hellooo!
哈啰
Hello?
我想带斯黛拉一起来旅行 逗她开心
I wanted to bring Stella on the trip to cheer her up.
她从没见过四季变化 但歌洛莉亚希望
She never sees seasons, but Gloria wanted one night
能有一晚只有我跟她在床上
with just the two of us in bed,
所以我做了通情达理的决定
so I did the only sensible thing.
你把她留在家给狗保姆照顾吗
You left her at home with a dog sitter?
在前面那家酒店给她开了个房间
Checked her in the hotel down the road.
我想灌歌洛莉亚多喝点酒
I'm trying to get some wine in Gloria
让她早早昏睡过去 我就能溜出去喂斯黛拉了
so she passes out early and I can sneak off and feed Stella.
前面那家酒店 你是指五星豪华丽兹酒店吗
The hotel down the road? You mean the Ritz?
我用会员积分换的 别激动
I had points. Calm down.
好酷啊 这个既是开瓶器也是瓶塞
Oh, how cool. This is both an opener and a stopper.
真不错
Nice.
看来这不仅对瓶子有此功用
Oh, I guess what it does for bottles,
对聊天也一样 开完即合
it also does for conversations.
等等 那不是... 罗纳多
Wait, is that -- Ronaldo!
米奇尔
Mitchell!
好巧啊
What a surprise.
这位是谁
And who is this?
我一直以为我才是你最性感的拉丁朋友
I always assumed I was your sexiest Latin friend.
这是歌洛莉亚 歌洛莉亚 这是罗纳多
This is Gloria. Gloria, Ronaldo.
-玻利维亚人吗 -危地马拉人
- Bolivian? ?- Guatemalan.
-委内瑞拉人吗 -哥伦比亚人
- Venezuelan? ?- Colombian.
看不懂这是在干嘛
Mm-hmm. ?Not sure what this is.
你来城里干什么呀
Um, so w-what are you doing in town?
就是来买点红酒 我要承办一个宴会
Oh, just picking up some wine for a party I'm catering...
在奥普拉·温弗瑞家
at Oprah Winfrey's.
-什么 -别骗人了
- What? - Stop it!
-这是了不起的事吗 -你少在那边装了
- Oh, what, is that a big deal? - Don't you be coy.
你明明知道刚才那一瞬间我就对你折服了
You know the power dynamic just shifted between us.
你们想的话 我可以带你们参加派对
If you want, I can get you two into the party.
-少来了 -你愿意帮我们吗
- Get out! - You would do that for us?
仅仅因为我很喜欢你
Only because I like you so much.
我也超喜欢你
I like you so much, too!
你们变脸变蛮快的嘛
That was a quick thaw.
但只能你们两人 不能带上卡梅隆
It can only be the two of you, though. No Cameron.
不然胡娇会杀了我
Pepper would kill me.
对了 小卡跟罗纳多的老公有积怨
Right. Cam's in a feud with Ronaldo's husband
他们争执奶酪拼盘应该配哪种饼干
over what type of cracker belongs on a cheese platter.
水饼干 奶酪才是主角
Water cracker. The cheese is the star.
-我们才不吵他们的架 -对
- This isn't our fight. - No.
我得走了 等会发地址给你
I have to run. I'll text you the address.
好的 再见
Okay. Bye-bye.
你敢信吗 我们要去奥普拉家参加派对了
Can you believe this? We're going to a party at Oprah's.
如果我们跟她成了朋友怎么办
What if we become friends with her?
如果我们有了自己的电视节目呢
What if we get our own TV show?
谁去接乔放学回家啊
Who's gonna pick up Joe from school?!
歌洛莉亚
Gloria...
我们请司机
we'll have drivers.
-周二公司 -周二公司
- Tuesday Company! - ?Tuesday Company!
小卡 米奇 克莱尔和我报名了街舞班
Cam, Mitch, Claire, and I signed up for a hip-hop class.
当他们让我们在登记墙上
We knew it was legit when they asked us
涂鸦我们的名字时 就知道这里很正宗
to graffiti our names on the sign-up wall.
右腿 踢起来
Right leg, come on.
双手抱胸 来
Unh. Wrap those arms, come on.
好
And yah!
我喜欢 做得好 各位
I like it. Nice job, everybody!
很棒 真棒
Great. That's great.
确定哥 这堂课太屌了
Hey, Sho Nuff. Bomb class.
是啊 太牛逼了
Yeah, yeah. Really sick.
你俩很来劲啊
Hey, man. You two were hitting it hard out there.
我很喜欢你们的动作
I was really believing your movements.
你是说我们做到了吗
Are you... saying we brought it?
我是说你们太赞了
I'm saying y'all crushed it.
保持 好吗
Keep it up. All right?
-好 -来击拳
- Okay. ?- Hit it.
好 就这样
All right. There you go.
-卡梅隆 -菲利普
- Cameron? ?- Philip?
-你听到了吗 -你是说我们的舞蹈老师说
- Did you hear that? - You mean when our dance instructor
我们差不多是街舞明星了吗
told us we were basically street-dance superstars?
你发现他只对我俩说吗
Did you notice how he singled us out?
他都没提到米奇或克莱尔
He didn't even mention Mitch or Claire.
仿佛是在说他们拖我们后腿了
It's like he's saying they're holding us back.
知道吗
Okay. You know what?
我们得赶紧摆脱累赘
We need to shed our dead-weight spouses.
世上没有比确定哥更让我
There is nobody I would rather impress more
-想打动的人了 -太对
- than Sho Nuff. - ?True dat.
不 太对兄只是个DJ 我才懒得鸟他呢
No, True Dat's just the DJ. I don't care what he thinks.
想不到小卡和我是很好的舞伴
Turns out, Cam and I make tremendous dance partners.
我们的身体很合拍
Our bodies are so in tune,
就像是我们完成了彼此的
it's like we finish each other's...
动作
...sequences.
菲尔开始跳 我就本能地完成了
Phil starts a move, and I instinctually complete it.
对 就像听起来一样强大
And, yeah, it's as powerful as it sounds.
天啊 你有没有想过
Oh, my gosh. Did you ever think
来自密苏里州的农场男孩
a farm boy from Missouri
和来自佛州基韦斯特的房地产经纪人
and -- and a real-estate agent from Key West, Florida,
将得到去久负盛名的
would get the opportunity to audition
周二公司试跳的机会吗
for the prestigious Tuesday Company?
费用只比普通课程多一点
And it only costs slightly more than regular classes.
我们可能成为自"榨出"和"果酱"后
We could be the greatest masters-level hip-hop duo
-最伟大的大师级别的街舞组合 -我知道
- since Pump Up and The Jam! - ?I know!
回访就在明天了 我们今晚得溜出来
Callback's tomorrow, so we'll have to sneak out tonight
进行最后的彩排
for a final rehearsal.
你带了服装吧 以防我们真被选上了呢
You -- You brought the outfit in case we got it, right?
"以防" 真好笑 菲尔
"In case"? Good one, Phil.
我很难抵抗手舞足蹈的诱惑 你呢
I'm having a hard time resisting dancing with joy, are you?
-葡萄藤下见 -好
- Me-Meet at the grapes. ?- Okay.
我找了好久才找到停车位
Man, it took forever to find a parking spot.
-来一口浓郁黏稠的卡本内就最好了 -不可以
- I could really use a sip of a chewy Cabernet. - You can't drink.
你得保持清醒 载我们其余人回家
You have to stay sober to drive the rest of us home.
等等 这就是我来这里的原因吗 当代驾司机
Wait, is that why I'm here? To be the designated driver?
如果你非得要个职称 算是吧
If you need a title, sure.
走前门声音太大
Okay, the front door's too loud.
走这里也能去车道
We can get to the driveway this way.
我看起来像是环球小姐
I look like Miss Universe.
你干什么 海莉说了别碰
What are you doing? Haley said not to touch that.
让我看看
?Let me see.
整齐的切口
Clean cut.
-是真钻 -别管了 走吧
- Those are real diamonds! - ?Leave 'em. Come on.
小卡 走这边
Cam, walk this way. Oh. Ooh, ooh, ooh!
混合金属现在很流行
Mixing metals is very in-fashion right now.
不不
No, no. Hey, hey, hey, hey.
18小时后 确定哥就要以1分到"屌炸"了
In 18 hours, Sho Nuff is gonna be rating our dance skills
来给我们的舞蹈评分了 快来练
on a scale of one to "Dayum"! Come on!
好了 好了
All right. All right.
坐这里
Butt...here.
再给你一个饼干
Just one more treat.
待着
Here.
我们快点
Shh. We'll just do this quick.
这就对了
Shh. Here you go.
真美
Gorgeous!
爸爸
Dad?
我还以为你是歌洛莉亚
I thought you were Gloria.
斯黛拉为什么在这里
Wh-Why is Stella here?
我之前打算在宾馆给她喂吃的
I was going to feed her at the hotel --
她很明显不太好
she's clearly in a bad way.
她把房间里搞得一团糟
She trashed the room.
看起来像是谁人乐队住过的
It looked like The Who was staying there.
所以我要把她藏在宾馆里
So, I'm gonna stash her in the guesthouse,
给她刷毛 直到她睡着
brush her fur until she goes to sleep.
斯黛拉
Stella!
什么
What?
我是舞会皇后吗
I am prom queen?!
不是艾希莉·沃尔斯吗
It's not -- It's not Ashley Walls
那个出车祸后获得了大家同情票的姑娘
who got the pity vote after her car accident?
谢谢
Thank you.
如果我们要去奥普拉所有重要的房间
Okay. Now we need to be strategic if we're gonna hit
那我们就得有策略 好吗
all of Oprah's important rooms, okay?
她的家庭办公室 礼品包装室
Her home office, her gift-wrapping room,
舒适毛衣的温度控制库
her temperature-controlled vault of cozy sweaters.
但如果她的挚友盖尔在呢
But what if Gayle is there?
我们要停下来跟她说话吗
Do we stop to talk to her?
不 不管小牌的盖尔 时间不够
No. No Gayle. There's no time.
我们在这小区
Okay, that-that's the third house
已经过了第三套房子了
in this compound that we passed.
我们怎么知道我们到了
How will we know when we get
奥普拉的...
to Oprah's actual hou--
天啊
Oh, my God.
好吧
Okay.
很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
-我提臀的动作快了一拍 -不不
- I was a beat early on the booty drop. - No, no, no.
怪我 是我吸胸的动作慢了一拍
It was me. I was a beat late on the chest pop.
这很奇怪 但我好紧张
It's weird, but I'm -- I'm nervous.
我也是 但是你知道吗
I am, too. But you know what?
我们只用放松
We -- We just have to relax
记住自己是谁 我们只是两个跳舞的人
and remember we're -- we're just a couple guys dancing.
我们在骗谁呢
Who are we kidding?!
能进入周二公司就太棒了
Getting Tuesday Company would be epic!
我知道 我们会有自己的舞房
I know! We get our own cubbies.
再也不用把钥匙和钱包集中放在角落里了
We don't have to throw our keys and wallet in the corner anymore.
周二狗狗团不是
Didn't the Tuesdoggs perform
在去年的女子篮球联盟全明星赛上表演了吗
at the WNBA All-Star Game last year?
这会改变我们的生活 但我们得别再说
It would be life-changing, but we have to stop talking about
这会有多棒了
how great it would be.
-这让我们迷失了 -对
- That's what's throwing us off. - ?Right.
现在我们就是
For now, it's -- We're just -- Hey. ?Hey.
-两个人 -在跳舞
- Here's two guys... ?- Dancing.
-我们在跳舞 -我们在跳舞
- We're dancing. Yeah. - We're dancing.
-我们从头开始 好 -嗯
- Let's take it from the top. All right. - Yep.
五六七八
Five, six, seven, eight, and...
怪我
And that's my bad.
你去哪儿了 我转身就发现你不见了
Where have you been? I turned around and you were gone.
我上了奥普拉的床
I was in Oprah's bed!
-猜猜她的睡眠指数 -我没必要
- Guess her sleep number. - I don't have to.
-我碰了她 我碰了奥普拉 -什么
- I touched her. I touched Oprah! ?- What?!
严格来说
Well, technically,
我用手指掠过了她的礼服边缘
I brushed the edge of her gown with my finger.
但是看着 我的伤口神奇般地愈合了
But look -- my cut's magically healed.
我听说有小象
And I heard they have baby elephants
载大家去南草坪
carrying everyone to the south lawn
去看真人扮演棋子的国际象棋赛 走吧
to see a living chess match. Let's go! ?
等等 不 歌洛莉亚 别
Wait, no, Gloria. Gloria, Come on.
我们说好只玩一小时
We said we'd only stay for an hour.
我们得回到平凡的生活中去了
We have to get back to our normal lives.
-怎么做得到 -我懂
- But how?! - I know.
别分开他们
Leave them.
听我的话 如果你有第二次机会找到真爱
Take it from me -- if you get a second chance at love,
要把握住
you grab it.
经历了失去它最好的朋友诺曼的打击
After the trauma of losing her best friend, Norman,
笼罩着斯黛拉的抑郁
Stella's veil of depression
都因为新恋情带来的希望消散了
was lifted by the promise of new romance.
她意识到她可以再次去爱
She realized she could love again.
你不能分开他们 克莱尔
You can't separate them, Claire.
我要把那只拖鞋带回家
I'm taking that slipper home with me.
冒着菲尔下次去你家时会看到的风险
And risk Phil seeing it the next time we're at your house?
别想了
Forget it.
斯黛拉也该玩够了 到此为止
Stella's had her fun. This is over.
你为什么就是不肯接受他们
Why is this so hard for you to accept?
是因为他们是一只狗和一只拖鞋吗
Is it because it's a dog and a slipper?
怪我
My bad.
-又是我 -不不不
- Again. ?- No, no. No, no.
怪我 我太独了
That's on me. I'm-I'm-I'm-I'm still in my head.
我们面对现实吧小卡 这不是因为紧张
Let's face it, Cam. This isn't about nerves.
这是因为我失去了曾有过的火花
It's about me losing whatever spark I once had.
就像有人把我身上的范儿
It's like someone sucked the funk
-都抽走了 -不 问题在我
- right out of me! - No, I'm the problem.
我就像丢掉了开启嘻哈范的钥匙一样
It's like I've lost the key to the lock on my pop.
你别带我自己去吧
Just...go on without me.
是我拖累了你 不能这样下去了
I'm holding you back! I mean, nuff is nuff.
或许鲍勃·贝司唱错了
Maybe Rob Base was wrong.
一个人才能办好事
It takes one to make a thing go right.
-我们会不会... -说吧
- Is it possible... ?- Just say it.
我们只不过是周一的舞者
...that we're just Monday dancers?
现在呢
Is it better?
不行 我还是能闻到一点大象味
No, I'm still getting a hint of elephant.
-下车 -我只是实话实说
- Get out. ?- W- I'm just being honest.
不 到家门前最后这十五米
No, we have to push the car
我们得推着车过去
the last 50 feet to the house...
这样就不会被人听到我们回来了
...so that they don't hear us coming.
我觉得我沾染了些许奥普拉的力气
I feel like some of Oprah's strength must've rubbed off on me.
我打赌我能把这台车抬起来
I bet I could carry this car up.
你确定车现在是空挡吗
Are you sure this is in neutral?
这是什么
What is this?!
你这个糖果盘是从奥普拉家偷的吗
Did you steal this candy dish from Oprah's house?
上面还刻了她的姓名缩写
It has her initials engraved.
我没忍住 我想要个纪念品
I couldn't help it. I wanted a souvenir.
但你说我们不能带回任何证据
But you said that we couldn't bring any evidence in here,
你甚至不准我拿派对上的纸巾
and you didn't even let me take the party napkin
上面印着她拥抱各种肤色孩子的卡通
that had a cartoon of her hugging children of many colors!
好吧 对不起
Okay, I'm sorry.
不如咱俩共同拥有这糖果盘的监护权如何
What if-what if we share custody of the candy dish?
那好吧
Okay, fine.
但所有节假日它都归我
But I get it for the holidays.
来了
Coming.
抱歉 我把钥匙忘在厅里了
Oh, hey, sorry. I forgot my keys in the drawing room.
我放哪去了
Okay, where did I put them?
应该就在这吧
They were right here, right?
就在我想的地方
And right where I thought I left them.
等一下 怎么回事
Wait a minute. What is that?
我的天
Oh, my God.
我的天 小皇冠裂缝了
Oh, my God! The tiara! It's cracked!
是谁干的
Who did this?!
我会查个究竟的
I'll get to the bottom of this.
我才不在乎那些低能的俗人怎么说
I don't care what some feeble-minded vulgarian says.
曼尼·迪尔加多知道怎么扮好侦探
Manny Delgado knows how to play the role of an inspector.
-我发短信叫大家下来 -谢谢你
- I'll text everyone to come downstairs. ?- Thank you.
糟了
No!
Oh, no.
尼玛
Oh, hell no.
好吧 等等 爸 我们得想个借口
Okay. Wait, wait, Dad. We need an excuse!
人们会奇怪我们怎么没睡的
People are gonna wonder why we weren't in bed.
告诉他们...
Um, tell them that, uh, uh...
我们在阳台是因为我看到了一头驼鹿
Oh! We were on the balcony because we saw a moose.
太蠢了
That's dumb.
告诉他们我在厨房给你热牛奶
We'll tell them I'm heating up some milk for you in the kitchen
因为你胃疼
because your stomach hurts.
为什么 因为我看到驼鹿吓到了吗
Why? Because I was upset that I saw a moose?
快穿上
Put this on.
-我扔早了 -我接晚了
- I was early. - I was late.
快 快
Hurry, hurry!
你身上还是有很重的大象味
I'm still getting strong notes of elephant off of you.
-你搞不好得把头发都剪了 -不要
- You may have to cut off all your hair. - No!
我知道大家都很好奇我为什么叫你们来
I'm sure you're wondering why I've gathered you all here.
小皇冠裂了 你在短信里说了
Uh, the tiara's cracked. You told us in your text.
但我没告诉你们 我发誓
What I didn't tell you is that I've vowed
要找出是谁干的
to find out who's responsible.
不 其实你说了 短信很长...
Well, no, actually, you did. It was a fairly long --
所有人都有嫌疑
Everyone's a suspect.
别看我 我根本没靠近过小皇冠
Don't look at me. I wasn't anywhere near it.
"真意外" 菲尔装无辜
What a surprise -- Phil feigning innocence.
人人都最喜欢你这个憨厚老爸是吧
You're just everyone's favorite Dad, right?
收到我短信时你在哪
Where were you when you got my text?
小卡他 胃疼
Cam's, uh, stomach was upset,
我在帮他热牛奶
and I was warming up some milk for him.
-克莱尔看到一头驼鹿 -是的
- Claire saw a moose. - ?I did.
所以收到短信时我们在阳台上
And that's why we were on the balcony when you texted us.
歌洛莉亚和我在活动室
Well, Gloria and I were in the den.
我出去散步时偶遇她
I ran into her on my way out to my walk,
然后我们决定一起赏月
and then we decided to watch the moon together.
赏月是吗
The moon, huh?
不太可能吧 因为今晚没有月亮
Seems unlikely given tonight is moonless!
没关系
No matter.
那你们有没有人经过这间房间
So, did any of you go through this room at any point?
在我听来所有人都在室内
Sounds to me like everybody was inside
做他们在做的事
doing whatever they were supposed to be doing.
那就怪了 因为我发现这扇门没关严
That's odd because I found this door slightly open,
那意味着你们有人出去了
which means one of you was outside.
等我查出是谁从这扇门出去了
When I find out who went out that door,
我很肯定他就是犯人
quite sure I'll have my culprit.
那是什么
Hey, what's that?
似乎是两个姜饼小人的下半身
It appears to be two bottom halves
被融合在一起了
of a gingerbread man melded together.
看起来像骨头 是块狗饼干
Uh, it looks like a bone. It's a dog treat.
不 那是人吃的饼干
No, it's a human treat,
做成骨头形状是因为富含钙质
and it's shaped like a bone because it's full of calcium.
我之前在吃这些饼干
I was snacking on them earlier in the day
肯定是掉了一块
and I must have dropped one.
真好吃
Mmm, they're delicious.
对身体还很有好处
And they're very good for you.
说得通
Checks out.
是楼上传来的
That's coming from upstairs!
不 是外面
No, outside.
歌洛莉亚 怎么会这样
Gloria, how did this happen?
我有个理论
I have a theory.
我有次读到过一头驼鹿把露营车给撞换挡了
I once read about a moose that knocked a camper out of neutral.
或许克莱尔之前看到的驼鹿也那样做了
Perhaps the moose Claire saw earlier did the same thing here.
-引擎盖还是热的 -那就别靠在上面
- The hood's warm. - Then don't lean on it.
我承认 米奇和我之前在屋外
I admit it! Mitch and I -- we were outside.
他想和我聊聊他和小卡
He wanted to talk to me about a problem
在基佬卧室里不和谐的问题
he's having with Cam in the gay bedroom.
这么说我不行就是有问题
Oh, so when it's me, it's a problem.
你不行就是因为健身累的
When it's you, it's what happens when you work out too much.
我们觉得冷 就坐进车里了
It got cold, we went inside the car,
我打开了暖气
I turned the heater on,
所以肯定是我不小心把车撞到了空挡
and I must have accidentally knocked it into neutral.
所以驼鹿来的时候 车早已蓄势待滑
So, it was all ready to roll when the moose showed up.
这个糖果盘怎么在这
Hey, uh, what's this candy dish doing here?
海莉 拜托 我在思考
Haley, please, I'm trying to think.
但那可能是证据
But it could be evidence.
网球场的灯怎么亮着
What are the lights doing on in the tennis court?!
这些椅子怎么会在这
Now why would these chairs be out here,
这些又与驼鹿有什么联系
and how do they connect to the moose?
这些脚印... 规律好奇怪啊
These footprints are in a... really weird pattern.
为什么这步伐感觉如此熟悉
Why do these steps feel so familiar?
我跟小卡来过这里
Cam and I were out here, um --
我们本来在厨房 然后听到外面有浣熊的声音
We were in the kitchen, and we heard a raccoon outside.
对啊对啊 所以我们出来了...
Yeah, yeah. So, we came out, we --
我们拿了凳子来... 来吓走它
we grabbed a couple chairs to -- to -- to scare it off.
我们这么... 这么拿着凳子
We held -- held them up like this,
然后呢... 追着那浣熊
and, um, chased the raccoon,
结果它跑进垃圾堆里 我们就...
but it ran into some trash cans and we were like...
然后它跑到球场这里来
And then, uh, it ran up the court this way... ?
然后又退了几步
...and then back a couple of steps
-又再往前了一次 -往前
- and then forward again and - Forward.
然后它最后转了一圈 往前跑
then it did a little spin. Forward, and
对 就这样
Yep. That was it.
接着它对我们冲过来 我们就
And then it came back at us, and we were like --
右左 右 右
Right, left. Right, right,
卷身 最后转
body roll, and spin.
然后它就跑了
And then, it was just gone.
刚才是什么玩意儿
What the hell was that?
这是什么鬼 我完全无法理解这些线索
What is any of this? I can't make sense of these clues.
哪有浣熊不会被巨大的驼鹿给吓跑啊
What kind of raccoon isn't scared off by the presence of a moose?
我们只需要知道
All we need to know
米奇尔 歌洛莉亚 小卡与菲尔
is that Mitchell, Gloria, Cam, and Phil
-是唯四嫌疑人 -才不是唯四
- are the four and only suspects. - Not only!
一个一个说 菲尔你先说
One at a time! Phil, go first.
这样压力好大啊
Well, that's a lot of pressure.
说
Speak!
那什么声音
What is that noise?
听起来像是一条狗在说"哈喽"
It's like a dog saying, "Hello."
听起来像加州犬吠驼鹿的声音啊
Sounds to me like a California barking moose.
从上面传来的
It came from up there.
我们刚才讲解追浣熊的事时 好合拍啊
We were really in-sync talking through that raccoon chase.
-感觉我们的拍子又重新合上了 -真的呢
- It felt like maybe we had our timing back again. - It really did.
或许刚才我们忘了舞蹈不是为了名气或荣耀
Maybe we forgot dance isn't about the fame or -- or glory,
而是用来对观众们诉说
but it's about telling a story that takes your audience
一段跌宕起伏的故事
on a journey that ebbs and flows.
跌宕起伏[艾博与弗洛/律动]
Ebb and Flow.
我们的嘻哈诨名就是这个了
I think we just found our hip-hop names.
杰
Jay!
-你带斯黛拉来了吗 -没有啊
- You brought Stella?! ?- No!
她自己跑来找我们了
She must have tracked us here.
你说什么啊 小姑娘
What's that, girl?
什么 家里的炉灶火没关吗
What? We left the stove on?
-真是怪事 -等等 稍等一下
- Well, that was weird. - Wait, wait. Whoa, whoa.
我的拖鞋为什么在这里面
What is my slipper doing in here?
我没说错吧 的确是有些冷
I'm not wrong. It's cold, huh?
亲爱的
Hey. Honey...
我们得谈谈这件事
We need to talk about this. ?
-斯黛拉 -她想要那个拖鞋啊 菲尔
- Um, Stella... - She wants the slipper, Phil.
天啊
Oh, my God.
为什么菲尔穿得像嘻哈男团的人
W-Why is Phil dressed like a Beastie Boy?
等等 等等
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
你们俩个不带我们跳嘻哈
You two did hip-hop without us! ?
是啦 因为你跟克莱尔是我们的累赘
Okay, be-because you and Claire were holding us back.
少来了 我们跳得跟你们一样好
Oh, please. We are just as good as you are.
-感觉有人想要来斗舞啊 -没有
- It sounds like somebody wants a dance-off. - No.
永远不会有人想要斗舞
No one ever wants a dance-off.
-菲尔 你为什么不直接跟我说 -省省吧 克莱尔
- Phil, why didn't you just tell me? - Save it, Claire.
我知道是你对我的熊熊拖鞋搞鬼
I know you put the hit out on my bear slippers.
这拖鞋很让人提不起性趣
Those are just very unsexy.
难道你就整天穿得很性感吗
Oh, 'cause you always dress so sexy?
来看看你今晚的睡衣
Let's check out this nightwear.
卢克的初中体育课短裤
Luke's junior high gym shorts,
而腰上的松紧带是用旧鞋带改的
and the drawstring is an old shoelace.
至少我不是那种花大钱
Well, at least I'm not one of those wives
在睡衣上面的那种败家老婆啊
that spends a fortune on lingerie.
你看 这鞋带断掉的时候
I mean, look, when the shoelace broke,
我用订书机修好了
I fixed it with a staple.
我们度假时为什么就不能来点激情呢
Well, why don't we add a little spice for our vacation?
歌洛莉亚就穿着及地的珠珠睡袍睡觉啊
I mean, Gloria wears a floor-length, beaded nightgown to bed.
等等 她才没有呢
Wait a second. No, she doesn't.
厉害了
Yes.
它网站上的图片看起来很舒适啊
It looked very comfortable on the website.
等一下 歌洛莉亚晚上跟米奇尔在一起
Wait a minute. Gloria was with Mitchell.
我们看看这里面有何乾坤
What have we got going on under here?!
你是想去哪里啊 穿这么衣冠楚楚
Okay, where were you going looking so dapper?!
衣冠楚楚 真的吗
Dapper? Really? Aww...
曼尼 曼尼
Oh! Ooh! Manny. Manny!
看看米奇尔舅舅的口袋里掉出了什么
Hey! Look what just fell out of Uncle Mitch's pocket!
第二个糖果盘...
A second candy dish...
-等等 -这上面有刻字
- Hold up. - This is monogrammed.
"M.O."
"M.O."?
你没带我就去米歇尔·奥巴马家吗
You went to Michelle Obama's without me?
你去奥普拉·温福瑞家没带我吗
You went to Oprah Winfrey's without me?!
歌洛莉亚 这是真的吗
Gloria, is this true?
你明明知道我对奥普拉有何感觉 她改变了我...
You know how I feel about Oprah. She changed my --
我修正一下
Excuse me.
她给了我改变自己人生的力量
She gave me the strength to change my own life!
小卡
Cam.
停下 停下
Stop. Stop!
都停下
Stop!!
我们忘记了重点是有人弄裂了
Have we all forgotten that somebody
我老板的小皇冠吗
cracked my boss's tiara?!
我可能被炒鱿鱼呢
I could get fired!
我碰过一次
Well, I touched it once,
有可能是我 我出钱修吧
so I might have done it. I'll pay for it.
等等 我跟小卡也碰了它
Hold on. Cam and I messed with it, too.
-我放我手上了 -我也试戴了
- I put it on my hand. ?- I tried it.
-我也有份 -行吧 这么看来
- Me, too. ?- Okay, okay, obviously,
大家都有份伸爪 我们一起出钱吧
everybody monkeyed around with it, so we'll all chip in.
真的吗
Really?
-真的 -谢谢你们
- Yes. - Thank you, guys.
大家都上床睡觉吧
Yeah, let's go to bed!
听我说 我没有要站菲尔这边 但短裤该洗了
Listen, not to take Phil's side, but you could wash those shorts
因为我能闻到一股浓浓的大象味
'cause I'm getting a strong whiff of elephant. ?
谢谢你帮忙我找凶手 曼尼
Thanks for trying to help, Manny.
看来我们永远不会知道到底是谁弄裂的了
I guess we'll really never know who broke that tiara.
小皇冠是我弄裂的
I broke the tiara.
我前一晚自己在这房子里
I was alone at the house the night before
来了个小小的私人品酒活动
doing a little private wine tasting.
我做了一个网站
I made a website,
我告诉大家怎么活
and I tell people how to live.
做个拿铁灌肠
Get a latte enema.
喝大海水
Drink ocean water.
我知道如果我告诉我家人"别碰"
I knew if I said to my family, "Do not touch",
这帮人里肯定会有傻子想去试戴
one of those bozos would have to try it on
接着就会觉得是自己弄裂的
and then think they cracked it themselves.
是的 我比别人以为的还聪明
That's right. I'm a little smarter than people think.
不过也是运气好 计划差点被那驼鹿给毁了
But lucky, too. That moose almost ruined everything.
否认这事实是没意义的
You know, there's no sense denying it.
我们的人生已经改变了
Life, as we know it, has changed.
是啊是啊 从今往后 你周二跳舞
Yeah, yeah. From now on, you'll be dancing on Tuesdays.
罗纳多打来的视频电话
Oh, Ronaldo's FaceTiming.
两位好啊
Hey guys.
听我说 奥普拉知道糖果碗的事
So... listen. Oprah knows about the candy dish.
我不知道你在说什么啊
I don't know what you're talking about.
这里有摄像头 米奇尔
There are cameras, Mitchell.
你得还回来
You need to bring it back.
你在哪里啊
Where are you?
我还在奥普拉家
I'm still here at Oprah's.
完全是个人意愿
Under my own free will.
我估计也还会继续留在这塔里
And, I'll probably stay here in this tower,
直到她拿回那个碗
untill she gets her dish back.
这碗对她挺有意义
It's quite meaningful.
是她偷...
She stole it from...
她从米歇尔·奥巴马那里"得到"的礼物
"got it" as a gift from Michelle Obama.
天啊
Oh my God.
米歇尔·奥巴马的糖果碗在我们手上
We have Michelle Obama's candy dish.
奥普拉·温福瑞有我们的电话
Oprah Winfrey has our number.
-好啊 -太好了
- OK. - Ok.